Gerelmaa Purevtseren

San Francisco, CA 94118 | C: 415-350-6688 | E: jenny_621@yahoo.com

Summary

Professional Interpreter with 3 years of experience helping diverse individuals. Moves easily between English and Mongolian without missing details. Focused on advancing vocabulary, idiomatic and cultural understanding with up-to-date knowledge.

Skills

- Problem resolution
- Team management
- Process improvement
- MS Office

- Operating systems
- Data collection and analysis
- Customer service
- Team building

Experience

MONGOLIAN INTERPRETER | 02/2017 to 08/2020

Human service - SAnfrancisco

- Over 5 years experience in Architectural design, development, implementation and support of application using ASP.NET, C#, JQuery, VB.Net, Joomla, C++, VBScript, SQL, Crystal reports, HTML, SQL server under Windows environment.
- Excellent knowledge in .NET Technology , ASP.NET,C++, ADO.NET .
- Implement Web Services and Components in .NET.
- Strong Data Base skills in SQL Server and Access.
- Hands on experience on Microsoft product like Visual Basic 6.0, Visual source safe and Visio.
- 1+years of Ruby on Rails development experience.
- Excellent communication and inter personnel skills.
- Exceptional ability to learn new concepts and hard working.
- Language proficient in English and Mongolian.
- Interpreted conference calls and other workplace communications in real-time.
- Delivered real-time, accurate oral translations and interpretations for clients.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER TEACHER | 08/2007 to 10/2010

Mongol deed university - Ulaanbaatar

- Developed and deployed oral and written assessment strategies for optimal review of student abilities.
- Lectured full classrooms of teach students on Programming language subjects.

PROGRAMMER | 07/2007 to 10/2010

Golomt bank - Ulaanbaatar

- Uncovered system issues by troubleshooting hardware and testing code at project intervals.
- Performed functional, non-functional, regression and performance tests for updated systems.

Education and Training

Computer Science And Technology "Altai"University - Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia | Bachelor of Science Software Engineer, 06/2007

Computer Science And Technology University - Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia | Master of Science Software Engineer, 06/2009

Harriet Fulbright College - Arlington, Virginia | Some College (No Degree) English Language Course

Intercultural Institute of California - San Francisco, CA | Some College (No Degree) English Language Course